alta.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy | Alta Ski Area | Alta, Utah

Last revised on November 6, 2018

Your privacy is important to us. Please read below to learn how we at Alta Ski Lifts Company ("Alta") collect, use, and secure your personal information. By using Alta’s website (“Site”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data as described herein.

**Information Collected From You**

We collect information from you, including information that directly or indirectly identifies you ("Personal Data") to provide you with the services and products we provide. For example:

  * When you place an order for tickets, services or other products, we request certain Personal Data from you on our order form. In some cases, you must provide:
    * Contact information such as first and last name, email address, phone number and billing address
    * Physical characteristics such as gender, height and photo
    * Financial information such as credit card number, expiration date and security code for billing purposes and to complete a transaction.
    * Location information such as which point of entry (“gate”) your pass was read at.
  * If you create an online account, you must provide contact information and a password. We retain information on your behalf, such as files that you store using our Site.

In addition to information we collect to complete a purchase, when you use our Site, we automatically collect information which helps us improve our Site. For example, we may collect the type of device you use, operating system version, the device identifier (or "UDID") and your location.  We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

**Cookies**

We use automatic data collection tools, which may include web beacons, cookies, embedded web links, and other commonly used information-gathering tools to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements around the site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these tools on an individual as well as aggregated basis. For instructions on how to control the use of cookies, visit your selected browser settings and follow the instructions to update or restrict the use of cookies at the browser level.

**How We Use the Information You give Us**

Alta handles personal information in the normal course and scope of business. Alta has a legitimate business interest in handling the information.  How we use the information may include:

  * Providing services through our website
  * Providing services at Alta
  * Requesting feedback
  * Marketing to guest and prospective guests
  * Providing services beyond Alta
  * Detecting and preventing fraud, abuse, and other harmful activity
  * Otherwise enhancing a quality skiing experience in the normal course of business

**How Your Information is Protected**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Data such as:

  * HTTPS encryption
  * Third-party payment providers
  * In-house & third-party network security administration and testing
  * Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) including Tokenization
  * Password protected accounts
  * Vulnerability scans, assessments and remediation
  * Penetration testing
  * Boundary and malware defense
  * Application software security
  * Server Firewall

**With Whom Your Information May Be Shared**

Alta may share information with third party service provides such as:

  * Credit card authorizations providers
  * Pass reciprocity entities
  * Data processors

Please be aware that our site contains links to 3rd party entities including other sites, social media features and widgets that are not owned or controlled by Alta.  Alta does not control and is not responsible for the privacy practices of such 3rd party entities. This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected by Alta.

**Sharing Personal Data by Law**

Alta may also handle this information pursuant to a legal obligation.

**What Choices Are Available?**

By default, opt-in checkboxes are left unchecked on alta.com, providing you with the option to opt-in for promotional communications.

If your Personal Data changes, you may request an update by contacting Alta.

If you live inside the European Economic Area, you may have the right, under certain circumstances, to request access, rectify, erase and restrict how we process your personal information. If you would like to exercise such rights, you may contact Alta or our privacy point of contact at:

Organization  
Alta Ski Area  
PO Box 8007  
Alta Utah United States 84092  
801-359-1078

Privacy Point of Contact  
Corporate Controller  
PO Box 8007  
Alta Utah United States 84092  
801-359-1078

**Children**  

Children are not eligible to make purchases on our Site and we ask that anyone under the age of 18 not submit any Personal Data to us. Alta does not knowingly collect Personal Data from anyone under the age of 18 on our site.

**Changes to our privacy statement**

We keep this privacy statement under regular review and will place any updates on our website. Paper copies of this privacy statement may also be obtained by contacting our Corporate Controller at the contact information above and requesting a paper copy.

**Opt Out Opportunity**

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Data used for certain purposes. If you no longer wish to receive promotional communications from us, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included at the bottom of each communication or by contacting us.  You cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails.
